[{"question": "A smaller lengthscale than the optimum will result in", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A more accurate model", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Overfitting", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Underfitting", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A linear model", "correct": false}], "tag": "hyperparameters lengthscale", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "When using a gaussian kernel, a point has near-zero covariance with another point if it is x distance away. x = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Lengthscale", "correct": false}, {"answer": "0.5*Lengthscale", "correct": false}, {"answer": "2*Lengthscale", "correct": true}, {"answer": "4*Lengthscale", "correct": false}], "tag": "hyperparameters lengthscale", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "To calculate the weights of a GPR model, we would need", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The x-values of the train data set", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The x-values of the test data set", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Noise in the data", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "hyperparameters", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "We can use multiple covariance functions in a single model", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "TRUE", "correct": true}, {"answer": "FALSE", "correct": false}, {"answer": "-", "correct": false}, {"answer": "-", "correct": false}], "tag": "kernel", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "A kernel is analogous to", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "a change of basis", "correct": true}, {"answer": "activation functions", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Both of the above", "correct": false}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "kernel", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "Which of the following are hyperparameters of a GPR model?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Lengthscale", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Noise", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Kernel", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "hyperparameters", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "Gaussian Process Regression is", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Deterministic and parametric", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Probabilistic and non-parametric", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Probabilistic and parametric", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Deterministic and non-parametric", "correct": false}], "tag": "kernel", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "The sum of two independent gaussian distribution functions is", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "a constant", "correct": false}, {"answer": "linear", "correct": false}, {"answer": "gaussian", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Periodic", "correct": false}], "tag": "kernel", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "The nature of extrapolation of a GPR model beyond the training data range would be determined by", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The kernel", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The number of data points", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Noise", "correct": false}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "kernel extrapolation", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}, {"question": "What would be the result if we use a linear kernal for a dataset that roughly follows a sinusoidal trend.", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "We will get a coding error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "the model will still perfectly fit", "correct": false}, {"answer": "the model will have a low uncertainty", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The model will have a high uncertainty ", "correct": true}], "tag": "kernel uncertainty", "lecture_file": "23_gp"}]